<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>C&#43;&#43; on Lviv Polytechnic National University</title>
    <link>https://lvivpnu.github.io/tags/c&#43;&#43;/</link>
    <description>Recent content in C&#43;&#43; on Lviv Polytechnic National University</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lvivpnu.github.io/tags/c++/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MPU-9250 Accelerometer, Gyroscope and Magnetometer Code</title>
      <link>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/mpu-9250-accelerometer-gyroscope-and-magnetometer-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/mpu-9250-accelerometer-gyroscope-and-magnetometer-code/</guid>
      <description>In this Article you will get the code and library for MPU-9250 module. Watch video instruction on how to use MPU-9250.
Get MPU-9250 Library from Github Data sheet for MPU-9250 MPU-9250 Register Map Get Library from Robojax.com I2C scanner Code and Video Guide to interfacing MPU9250 Gyroscope, Magnetometer and Accelerometer with a Raspberry Pi Arduino Nano: Accelerometer Gyroscope Compass MPU9250 I2C Sensor With Visuino Drivers for MPU9250 IMU Sensor /* * Library: https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Awesome C&#43;&#43;</title>
      <link>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/awesome-cpp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 14:51:12 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/awesome-cpp/</guid>
      <description>Awesome C++
Standard Libraries Frameworks Artificial Intelligence Asynchronous Event Loop Audio Biology BitTorrent CLI Compression Concurrency Containers Cryptography Database Debug Game Engine GUI Graphics Image Processing Internationalization Inter-process communication JSON Logging Machine Learning Math Memory Allocation Multimedia Networking PDF Physics Regular Expression Robotics Scientific Computing Scripting Serialization Sorting Video Virtual Machines Web Application Framework XML Miscellaneous Software
Compiler Online Compiler Debugger Integrated Development Environment Build Systems Static Code Analysis Coding Style Tools Resources</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
