<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Lviv Polytechnic National University</title>
    <link>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Lviv Polytechnic National University</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 10:35:36 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to copy files in Go</title>
      <link>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/how_to_copy_files_in_go/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 10:35:36 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/how_to_copy_files_in_go/</guid>
      <description>A robust and efficient copy is conceptually simple, but not simple to implement due to the need to handle a number of edge cases and system limitations that are imposed by the target operating system and it&amp;rsquo;s configuration.
If you simply want to make a duplicate of the existing file you can use os.Link(srcName, dstName). This avoids having to move bytes around in the application and saves disk space. For large files, this is a significant time and space saving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MySQL Export Table to CSV</title>
      <link>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/mysql_export_table_to_csv/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 12:52:36 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/mysql_export_table_to_csv/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes we need keed data in some useful format and read it by available methods like Microsoft Excel, Google Spreadsheet, Libre Office, or something like that. In this post, I will show various techniques of how to export MySQL tables to a CSV file. The CSV stands for comma separated values. It will be useful to have data from MySQL database in CSV file format because you can analyze and format the data in the way you want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A FIFO Buffer Implementation</title>
      <link>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/a_fifo_buffer_implementation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 12:52:36 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/a_fifo_buffer_implementation/</guid>
      <description>A FIFO buffer is a useful way of storing data that arrives to a microcontroller peripheral asynchronously but cannot be read immediately. One example is storing bytes incoming on a UART. Buffering the bytes eases the real-time requirements for the embedded firmware.
A FIFO buffer stores data on a first-in, first-out basis. The storage structure is typically an array of contiguous memory. Data is written to the “head” of the buffer and read from the “tail”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Webcam Streaming using VLC on the Command Line</title>
      <link>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/live-webcam-streaming-using-vlc-on-the-command-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/live-webcam-streaming-using-vlc-on-the-command-line/</guid>
      <description>The following are notes on using VLC as both server and server to stream a webcam from a ender across a LAN to multiple receivers. It focusses only on internal LAN streaming, using RTSP, UDP and RTP as the streaming solutions, and working via the command line in Linux. VLC offers other form of streaming (e.g. HTTP, which are covered in some of my older notes) and the GUI is quite good for selecting streaming options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Operating Systems for ASUS Tinker Board</title>
      <link>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/os-for-asus-tinker-board/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/os-for-asus-tinker-board/</guid>
      <description>Hi dear reader. In previews article I had post How to connect DSI and CSI cable to tinker board with a some Frequently Asked Question. In this Article I had collected all available OS for single-board computer ASUS Tinker Board. Based on this computer i will to construct my robot with AI implementation and computer vision. Actually this the first reason why i had select Tinker Board that based on Rockchip RK3288 processor with 4x Cores &amp;ldquo;Cortex-A17&amp;rdquo; with frequency 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to connect DSI and CSI cable to tinker board</title>
      <link>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/how-to-connect-dsi-and-csi-cable-to-tinker-board/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/how-to-connect-dsi-and-csi-cable-to-tinker-board/</guid>
      <description>DSI, CSI cable can be use will no difference, those cable is the same. CSI connect to the middle of tinker board, please refer icon print on board as follows: DSI connect to the boundary of tinker board, please refer icon print on board as follows:
DSI panel need extra 5V power. You can USB to supply, or thinker board can output 5V by GPIO PIN, red line is for positive(+)，black line is for negative(-) , as follow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSH Examples, Tips &amp; Tunnels</title>
      <link>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/ssh-examples-tips-tunnels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/ssh-examples-tips-tunnels/</guid>
      <description>Practical SSH examples to take your remote system admin game to the next level. Commands and tips to not only use SSH but master ways to move around the network.
Knowing a few ssh tricks will benefit any system administrator, network engineer or security professional.
Practical SSH examples
SSH Socks Proxy SSH Tunnel (Port Forward) SSH Tunnel to Secondary Host Reverse SSH Tunnel SSH Reverse Proxy Establish VPN over SSH Copy your SSH key (ssh-copy-id) Run Command Remotely (non-interactive) Remote Packet Capture &amp;amp; View in Wireshark SSH Copy Folder from Local to Remote Remote GUI Applications with SSH x11 Forwarding12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mathematics Primer for 3D Software Developer (Coordinate Systems)</title>
      <link>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/math-primer-coordinate-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 14:51:12 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/math-primer-coordinate-systems/</guid>
      <description>This article assumes you have a minimum understanding vectors, and matrices. I will simply show applications of vectors and matrices and how they apply to game programming.
In this article, I would like to provide a brief math primer for people who would like to get involved in game programming. This is not an exhaustive explanation of all the math theory that one will have to know in order to be a successful game programmer, but it’s the very minimum amount of information that is necessary to know before you can begin as a game programmer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MPU-9250 Accelerometer, Gyroscope and Magnetometer Code</title>
      <link>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/mpu-9250-accelerometer-gyroscope-and-magnetometer-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/mpu-9250-accelerometer-gyroscope-and-magnetometer-code/</guid>
      <description>In this Article you will get the code and library for MPU-9250 module. Watch video instruction on how to use MPU-9250.
Get MPU-9250 Library from Github Data sheet for MPU-9250 MPU-9250 Register Map Get Library from Robojax.com I2C scanner Code and Video Guide to interfacing MPU9250 Gyroscope, Magnetometer and Accelerometer with a Raspberry Pi Arduino Nano: Accelerometer Gyroscope Compass MPU9250 I2C Sensor With Visuino Drivers for MPU9250 IMU Sensor /* * Library: https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Awesome C&#43;&#43;</title>
      <link>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/awesome-cpp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 14:51:12 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/awesome-cpp/</guid>
      <description>Awesome C++
Standard Libraries Frameworks Artificial Intelligence Asynchronous Event Loop Audio Biology BitTorrent CLI Compression Concurrency Containers Cryptography Database Debug Game Engine GUI Graphics Image Processing Internationalization Inter-process communication JSON Logging Machine Learning Math Memory Allocation Multimedia Networking PDF Physics Regular Expression Robotics Scientific Computing Scripting Serialization Sorting Video Virtual Machines Web Application Framework XML Miscellaneous Software
Compiler Online Compiler Debugger Integrated Development Environment Build Systems Static Code Analysis Coding Style Tools Resources</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drupal8 - Unable to determine class for field...</title>
      <link>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/drupal8-unable-to-determine-field/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 12:52:36 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/drupal8-unable-to-determine-field/</guid>
      <description>One possible way is that your module is missing from the codebase or has been improperly uninstalled and you&amp;rsquo;ve still a field which is using that missing module.
Try the following drush commands to remove the broken field:
drush sqlq &amp;#34;DELETE FROM cache_config&amp;#34; drush sqlq &amp;#34;DELETE FROM config WHERE name = &amp;#39;field.storage.xxx.xxx&amp;#39; OR data LIKE &amp;#39;%field.storage.xxx.xxx%&amp;#39;&amp;#34; drush sqlq &amp;#34;DELETE FROM config_snapshot WHERE name = &amp;#39;field.storage.xxx.xxx&amp;#39; OR data LIKE &amp;#39;%field.storage.xxx.xxx%&amp;#39;&amp;#34; Warning: Don&amp;rsquo;t execute above commands on master/live database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Back to Top&#39; Button for your website</title>
      <link>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/back-to-op-button-to-yourwebsite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 12:52:36 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/back-to-op-button-to-yourwebsite/</guid>
      <description>A Back To Top button is something that a lot of you have probably seen on many websites. It’s that arrow that appears at the bottom right or left corner of a web page when you start scrolling it. When clicked, it brings you back to the top of the page.
If you want to add a back to top button while you&amp;rsquo;re still designing a website, or just curious about how you can build one on your own, this article for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use Jekyll Docker container</title>
      <link>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/how-to-use-jekyll-container/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 12:52:36 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lvivpnu.github.io/blog/how-to-use-jekyll-container/</guid>
      <description>Jekyll&amp;rsquo;s Docker Container with Demo Content and demo site.
Plugins included:
- Jekyll: 3.8.3 -- jekyll-paginate -- jekyll-sitemap -- jekyll-feed -- jekyll-multisite -- jekyll-github-metadata -- jekyll-seo-tag -- jekyll-watch -- jekyll-sass-converter -- jekyll-assets -- jekyll-multiple-languages-plugin - Compass: 1.0.3 - NodeJS: 8.9.3 -- NPM: 5.5.1 -- Yarn: 1.3.2 The first of all: Install Docker:
On Linux Ubuntu/Debian:
https://docs.docker.com/install/linux/docker-ce/ubuntu/ https://docs.docker.com/install/linux/docker-ce/debian/
On MacOS:
https://docs.docker.com/docker-for-mac/install/
On Windows:
https://docs.docker.com/docker-for-windows/install/
Install Docker Compose:
https://docs.docker.com/compose/install/ Download repository:
git clone git@github.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
